{
    "id": "85a4eea4d0ed482fb312ddcd925831c3",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He lives in a world of ……………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fantastic",
                "fantastical",
                "fantasy"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "At last, a …………. gentleman came to her rescue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "chivalrous",
                "chivalry"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ……….. enough to get a good job at the age of twenty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fortune",
                "fortunate",
                "fortunately"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ……....….. the dog, it will attack you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "provoke",
                "provocative",
                "provocatively"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I met my friend, he smiled ………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "amicable",
                "amicably"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Scientists are engaged in the …………... of the Antarctic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "explore",
                "exploration",
                "exploring"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw the …………. in the papers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "announce",
                "announcing",
                "announcement"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The student asked the teacher to …….....…… the question.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "simple",
                "simplify",
                "simplification"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Some of our neighboring countries are ……....……. towards our country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hostile",
                "hostility"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Her dance ………… was superb.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "perform",
                "performing",
                "performance"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We go to the beach ……………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "occasional",
                "occasionally"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Ravi pretends to be every one’s friend. But there is no …………… in what he says.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sincere",
                "sincerely",
                "sincerity"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}